#Web Software Engineer @ <u>Anthony Maki</u>

SUMMARY

Four years into his software career, Anthony (he/they) enjoys creating technology experiences that materially improve the everyday person's quality of life. By curious necessity he's worn many hats, but specializes in no-8 full-stack web apps, composed of serverless & Node-based back-ends & React-inspired front-ends. He nurtures an appreciation for continued education, design systems, industry best practices, & open source code. Anthony looks forward to collaborating on socially conscious products.

EXPERIENCE

——FROM→>>—To	ROLE	ORG	DESCRIPTION
2019-02 2019-10		<u>Atomic</u> <u>Data</u>	* Facilitated all parts of SDLC * Created team & project documentation * Served on-call on weekly rotation * Revived legacy RoR app, reduced LOC, fixed bugs, & wrote features * Co-wrote custom WP brand site with stock locator & customer contact * Wrote stateful component & API code for insurance enrollment portal
2018-03 2018-05	JavaScript Developer	<u>Best Buy</u>	* Wrote team & project documentation * Co-wrote A/B tests on .com with Optimizely API * Liaised with product teams for test planning * Built MVP internal test dashboard with multiple API integrations
2017-07 2017-09	Developer	<u>Dealer</u> <u>Teamwork</u>	* Wrote stateful component, CSS, & product code * Transitioned from Angular 1.x to 2+ conventions * Absorbed more of PHP legacy app into SPA * Architected first CI/CD & DR pipelines
2016-11 2017-07	Technology Consultant	<u>Azend</u>	* Developed mobile stories, fixed CF bugs, & shipped to app stores * Co-wrote component & CSS code for beta product & fixed Java bugs * Started project analysis & development on Dealer Teamwork product

VOLUNTEERING

EDUCATION

——FROM	То	Role	Org	FROM ->>	То	CREDENTIAL	Org
2012-08 p	present	Assistant Head Election Judge	Minneapolis Elections & Voter Services	2015-11	2016-09	Certificate, Full Stack Software Engineering	<u>Prime Digital</u> <u>Academy</u>
2017-11 2	2018-02	Peer Mentor	Prime Digital Academy	2010-01	2013-05	AA, Liberal Arts (unfinished)	Minneapolis Community & Technical College
				2011-01	2011-04	Certificate, Political Journalism	<u>Georgetown</u> <u>University</u>

SKILLS & LANGUAGES

LEARNING				→>─ NATIVE
* C# * ColdFusion * Dart / Flutter * Java / Kotlin * Nix * Finnish * French * Rust * Swift	* Back-ends: * Apache * Express * Nginx * CI/CD: * Bash / Zshell * CircleCI * Codeship * Docker * Jenkins * Travis CI * YAML * i18n / a11y * Python * Ruby * SQL: * MSSQL * MySQL * PostgreSQL	* APIs: * AWS * GCP * Heroku * Vercel * NoSQL: * Firebase * GraphQL * MongoDB * Supabase * PHP * Spanish * Testing: * AVA * Git Hooks * Jest * TypeScript * Webpack	* CSS / PostCSS * Front-ends:	* English